[ {
  "num" : "0",
  "question" : "ㅁㄹㅌ",
  "answer" : "마라톤"
}, {
  "num" : "1",
  "question" : "ㅁㄹㄸㄱ",
  "answer" : "멀리뛰기"
}, {
  "num" : "2",
  "question" : "ㄴㅇㄸㄱ",
  "answer" : "높이뛰기"
}, {
  "num" : "3",
  "question" : "ㅈㄷㄴㅇㄸㄱ",
  "answer" : "장대높이뛰기"
}, {
  "num" : "4",
  "question" : "ㅊㄷㅈㄱ",
  "answer" : "창던지기"
}, {
  "num" : "5",
  "question" : "ㅇㅂㄷㅈㄱ",
  "answer" : "원반던지기"
}, {
  "num" : "6",
  "question" : "ㅍㅎㄷㅈㄱ",
  "answer" : "포환던지기"
}, {
  "num" : "7",
  "question" : "ㅊㄱ",
  "answer" : "축구"
}, {
  "num" : "8",
  "question" : "ㄴㄱ",
  "answer" : "농구"
}, {
  "num" : "9",
  "question" : "ㅂㄱ",
  "answer" : "배구"
}, {
  "num" : "10",
  "question" : "ㅎㄷㅂ",
  "answer" : "핸드볼"
}, {
  "num" : "11",
  "question" : "ㅇㄱ",
  "answer" : "야구"
}, {
  "num" : "12",
  "question" : "ㅍㄷㅎㅋ",
  "answer" : "필드하키"
}, {
  "num" : "13",
  "question" : "ㄹㅂ",
  "answer" : "럭비"
}, {
  "num" : "14",
  "question" : "ㅁㅅㅊㄱ",
  "answer" : "미식축구"
}, {
  "num" : "15",
  "question" : "ㄷㄱ",
  "answer" : "당구"
}, {
  "num" : "16",
  "question" : "ㄱㅍ",
  "answer" : "골프"
}, {
  "num" : "17",
  "question" : "ㅋㄹㅋ",
  "answer" : "크리켓"
}, {
  "num" : "18",
  "question" : "ㅅㅍㅌㅋㄹ",
  "answer" : "세팍타크로"
}, {
  "num" : "19",
  "question" : "ㅌㅂ",
  "answer" : "티볼"
}, {
  "num" : "20",
  "question" : "ㅈㄱ",
  "answer" : "족구"
}, {
  "num" : "21",
  "question" : "ㄱㅇㅌㅂ",
  "answer" : "게이트볼"
}, {
  "num" : "22",
  "question" : "ㅅㄱ",
  "answer" : "수구"
}, {
  "num" : "23",
  "question" : "ㅍㄱ",
  "answer" : "피구"
}, {
  "num" : "24",
  "question" : "ㅂㄹ",
  "answer" : "볼링"
}, {
  "num" : "25",
  "question" : "ㅌㄴㅅ",
  "answer" : "테니스"
}, {
  "num" : "26",
  "question" : "ㅂㄷㅁㅌ",
  "answer" : "배드민턴"
}, {
  "num" : "27",
  "question" : "ㅅㅋㅅ",
  "answer" : "스쿼시"
}, {
  "num" : "28",
  "question" : "ㅈㄱ",
  "answer" : "정구"
}, {
  "num" : "29",
  "question" : "ㅌㄱ",
  "answer" : "탁구"
}, {
  "num" : "30",
  "question" : "ㅈㅇㅎ",
  "answer" : "자유형"
}, {
  "num" : "31",
  "question" : "ㅂㅇ",
  "answer" : "배영"
}, {
  "num" : "32",
  "question" : "ㅍㅇ",
  "answer" : "평영"
}, {
  "num" : "33",
  "question" : "ㅈㅇ",
  "answer" : "접영"
}, {
  "num" : "34",
  "question" : "ㄷㅇㅂ",
  "answer" : "다이빙"
}, {
  "num" : "35",
  "question" : "ㅅㄱ",
  "answer" : "수구"
}, {
  "num" : "36",
  "question" : "ㅈㅈ",
  "answer" : "조정"
}, {
  "num" : "37",
  "question" : "ㄱㄱㅊㅈ",
  "answer" : "기계체조"
}, {
  "num" : "38",
  "question" : "ㅇㄷ",
  "answer" : "역도"
}, {
  "num" : "39",
  "question" : "ㅌㄱㄷ",
  "answer" : "태권도"
}, {
  "num" : "40",
  "question" : "ㅌㄱ",
  "answer" : "택견"
}, {
  "num" : "41",
  "question" : "ㅋㅍ",
  "answer" : "쿵푸"
}, {
  "num" : "42",
  "question" : "ㅆㄹ",
  "answer" : "씨름"
}, {
  "num" : "43",
  "question" : "ㄱㄹㅌ",
  "answer" : "가라테"
}, {
  "num" : "44",
  "question" : "ㅇㄷ",
  "answer" : "유도"
}, {
  "num" : "45",
  "question" : "ㅂㅅ",
  "answer" : "복싱"
}, {
  "num" : "46",
  "question" : "ㅋㅂㅅ",
  "answer" : "킥복싱"
}, {
  "num" : "47",
  "question" : "ㄹㅅㄹ",
  "answer" : "레슬링"
}, {
  "num" : "48",
  "question" : "ㅍㅆㄹ",
  "answer" : "팔씨름"
}, {
  "num" : "49",
  "question" : "ㅈㅈㅅ",
  "answer" : "주짓수"
}, {
  "num" : "50",
  "question" : "ㅍㅅ",
  "answer" : "펜싱"
}, {
  "num" : "51",
  "question" : "ㅎㄱㄷ",
  "answer" : "합기도"
}, {
  "num" : "52",
  "question" : "ㅇㄱ",
  "answer" : "양궁"
}, {
  "num" : "53",
  "question" : "ㅅㅁ",
  "answer" : "승마"
}, {
  "num" : "54",
  "question" : "ㅅㅍㄷ ㅅㅋㅇㅌ",
  "answer" : "스피드 스케이팅"
}, {
  "num" : "55",
  "question" : "ㅍㄱ ㅅㅋㅇㅌ",
  "answer" : "피겨 스케이팅"
}, {
  "num" : "56",
  "question" : "ㅅㅌㅌㄹ",
  "answer" : "쇼트트랙"
}, {
  "num" : "57",
  "question" : "ㅇㅇㅅㅎㅋ",
  "answer" : "아이스하키"
}, {
  "num" : "58",
  "question" : "ㅇㅍㅇ ㅅㅋ",
  "answer" : "알파인 스키"
}, {
  "num" : "59",
  "question" : "ㄴㄹㄷ ㅅㅋ",
  "answer" : "노르딕 스키"
}, {
  "num" : "60",
  "question" : "ㅍㄹㅅㅌㅇ ㅅㅋ",
  "answer" : "프리스타일 스키"
}, {
  "num" : "61",
  "question" : "ㅆㅇㅋ",
  "answer" : "싸이클"
}, {
  "num" : "62",
  "question" : "ㄱㄷ",
  "answer" : "검도"
}, {
  "num" : "63",
  "question" : "ㄹㄷㅊㅈ",
  "answer" : "리듬체조"
}, {
  "num" : "64",
  "question" : "ㅅㄱ",
  "answer" : "사격"
}, {
  "num" : "65",
  "question" : "ㅇㅌ",
  "answer" : "요트"
}, {
  "num" : "66",
  "question" : "ㅋㄴ",
  "answer" : "카누"
}, {
  "num" : "67",
  "question" : "ㅌㄹㅇㅇㅅㄹ",
  "answer" : "트라이애슬론"
}, {
  "num" : "68",
  "question" : "ㅅㅋㅇㅌㅂㄷ",
  "answer" : "스케이트보드"
}, {
  "num" : "69",
  "question" : "ㅅㅍㅊ ㅋㄹㅇㅁ",
  "answer" : "스포츠 클라이밍"
}, {
  "num" : "70",
  "question" : "ㅅㅍ",
  "answer" : "서핑"
}, {
  "num" : "71",
  "question" : "ㄹㅈ",
  "answer" : "루지"
}, {
  "num" : "72",
  "question" : "ㅂㅇㅇㅅㄹ",
  "answer" : "바이애슬론"
}, {
  "num" : "73",
  "question" : "ㅂㅅㄹㅇ",
  "answer" : "봅슬레이"
}, {
  "num" : "74",
  "question" : "ㅅㅋㄹㅌ",
  "answer" : "스켈레톤"
}, {
  "num" : "75",
  "question" : "ㅋㄹ",
  "answer" : "컬링"
}, {
  "num" : "76",
  "question" : "ㅍㅅ",
  "answer" : "풋살"
}, {
  "num" : "77",
  "question" : "ㅂㅇㄱ",
  "answer" : "발야구"
}, {
  "num" : "78",
  "question" : "ㅅㅁ",
  "answer" : "스모"
}, {
  "num" : "79",
  "question" : "ㅅㄷㄸㄱ",
  "answer" : "세단뛰기"
}, {
  "num" : "80",
  "question" : "ㅎㅁㄷㅈㄱ",
  "answer" : "해머던지기"
}, {
  "num" : "81",
  "question" : "ㅎㄷ",
  "answer" : "허들"
}, {
  "num" : "82",
  "question" : "ㅅㄴㅂㄷ",
  "answer" : "스노보드"
}, {
  "num" : "83",
  "question" : "ㅇㅌㅅㅌ ㅅㅇㅁ",
  "answer" : "아티스틱 스위밍"
}, {
  "num" : "84",
  "question" : "ㅋㄹㅅㅋㅌㄹ ㅅㅋ",
  "answer" : "크로스컨트리 스키"
}, {
  "num" : "85",
  "question" : "ㅅㅋㅈㅍ",
  "answer" : "스키점프"
}, {
  "num" : "86",
  "question" : "ㄱㅁ",
  "answer" : "경마"
}, {
  "num" : "87",
  "question" : "ㄷㅌ",
  "answer" : "다트"
}, {
  "num" : "88",
  "question" : "ㅍㅋㅂ",
  "answer" : "포켓볼"
}, {
  "num" : "89",
  "question" : "ㅂㅊㅂㄹㅂ",
  "answer" : "비치발리볼"
}, {
  "num" : "90",
  "question" : "ㅅㅍㅌㅂ",
  "answer" : "소프트볼"
}, {
  "num" : "91",
  "question" : "ㄷㄹㄱ",
  "answer" : "달리기"
}, {
  "num" : "92",
  "question" : "ㄱㅈ",
  "answer" : "계주"
}, {
  "num" : "93",
  "question" : "ㅈㅎㄱㅌㄱ",
  "answer" : "종합격투기"
}, {
  "num" : "94",
  "question" : "ㅁㅇㅌㅇ",
  "answer" : "무에타이"
}, {
  "num" : "95",
  "question" : "ㅋㅍㅇㄹ",
  "answer" : "카포에라"
}, {
  "num" : "96",
  "question" : "ㅈㄴㄱ",
  "answer" : "줄넘기"
}, {
  "num" : "97",
  "question" : "ㅋㅂㄷ",
  "answer" : "카바디"
}, {
  "num" : "98",
  "question" : "ㅅㅋㅂㄷㅇㅂ",
  "answer" : "스쿠버다이빙"
}, {
  "num" : "99",
  "question" : "ㅍㄹㄱㄹㅇㄷ",
  "answer" : "패러글라이딩"
} ]